<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Co2 on Love Nature</title>
    <link>https://naturenotclimate.github.io/LoveNature/tags/co2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Co2 on Love Nature</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Open</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 01:47:03 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naturenotclimate.github.io/LoveNature/tags/co2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature suffers because of the climate hysteria</title>
      <link>https://naturenotclimate.github.io/LoveNature/post/nature-suffers-because-of-climate-hysteria/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 01:47:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naturenotclimate.github.io/LoveNature/post/nature-suffers-because-of-climate-hysteria/</guid>
      <description>Watching the destruction of our planet on the travels to tropical expeditions is rough. It always hurts, and it makes many of us biologists cynical about the future. When in the tropics, we are constantly terrorized by the destruction of what we love and therefore study. It is like we are forced to watch our loved ones suffer. Most of us know very well that the most people’s love for nature has been hijacked and that this is the result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Wrong With the Future of Energy</title>
      <link>https://naturenotclimate.github.io/LoveNature/post/what-is-wrong-with-the-future-of-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 17:35:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naturenotclimate.github.io/LoveNature/post/what-is-wrong-with-the-future-of-energy/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; Swindling with the future of energy &amp;ndash; I find it difficult to accept that in our modern technological society, we promote the use of old and outdated technologies such as solar cells and wind driven dynamo’s. These sources of energy are inferior to what we are currently capable of. Oddly enough, during what is perceived a crisis, the climate lobby has turned the tables on technology, which is now following the lead of swindlers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>