<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scam on Love Nature</title>
    <link>https://naturenotclimate.github.io/LoveNature/tags/scam/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scam on Love Nature</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Open</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 12:06:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://naturenotclimate.github.io/LoveNature/tags/scam/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate funded science hypes are nothing new: the fat scare</title>
      <link>https://naturenotclimate.github.io/LoveNature/post/fat-scare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 12:06:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naturenotclimate.github.io/LoveNature/post/fat-scare/</guid>
      <description>You have probably heard of the acid rain scare of the seventies, a hype based not on science, but one solitary observation in a population of trees. Another such 1970’s science-fad was global cooling, a group of climatologists predicted that our earth was going to become a ball of ice because of a few years of lower average temperatures. Both unfounded hypes led to large and futile governmental spending. In nutrition science, there have also been plenty of memes that illegitimately dominated the scientific field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A scam with devastating consequences</title>
      <link>https://naturenotclimate.github.io/LoveNature/post/scam-with-devastating-consequences/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 17:35:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naturenotclimate.github.io/LoveNature/post/scam-with-devastating-consequences/</guid>
      <description>I work on the frontlines of tropical forests protection, right there where the chainsaws and the fires delete pristine forests the size of countries. During my work, I have never seen any signs of damage caused by climate change. At this moment, the destruction of tropical forests is at an all time high and accellerating, and yet very few people care, because their focus has been diverted.
![deforestation][deforestation of the tropics is increasing]</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>